Wait. so if I'm talking to a guy and he's
smiling. it's just out of politeness.
Or he likes you.
See you tomorrow.
Unless they lock us down.
Oh. well. if they do. I'll just see you
out in the wastelands then.
Goodbye!
Hello. stranger.
Did you get called back into the office?
Yep.
So what have you been up to for.
like. what. two years?
Baking. gardening...
Hey!
Marry me.
Excuse me?
My grandparents went
on eight dates. and they got married
and they've been married
for 50 years.
So what. go on eight dates
with you. and then...
Well. we don't have to get married
if you don't want. obviously.
We can start small. go for coffee?
Oh. you ordered for us.
Oh. hey. I have this really annoying
work party next Saturday.
I can't go.
Well. it's compulsory.
For you. maybe.
You want to come to a party next Saturday?
Sure.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Where are you going?
I'm not telling you.
Very nice.
It's okay.
I would just loosen up a bit.
Yeah.
Well. I'm going to order my ride.
Where's Pop?
I think he's in the bedroom.
All righty.
Have fun.
I will. See ya.
Hey. Pop. I'm off.
Okay.
You okay?
Is it just you?
It wasn't an old person's accident.
I blacked out for a second.
What? What do you mean?
Yeah. I stood up too fast.
Let's have a look. Come on.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Let's get you in the shower. eh?
There you go.
You.... you go.
No. I'm going to call and cancel.
You can't cancel now.
You've been locked in the house
for two years.
This is not your problem.
Go!
Sorry. I'm a little bit late.
Thanks for coming.
Shall we?
Yeah.
So this is where you work?
No.
We're in some hipster warehouse
down the road.
This is the new Overlord's headquarters.
We got absorbed by a big American company
last month. so tensions are high.
These two look like
nice. sensible. normal people. right?
Yep.
I think so.
We don't have to stay long.
Fuck it.
I've got to wear heels.
Okay.
Oh. God.
This was a terrible idea.
Emily!
Come!
... started it about eight times.
but we work very well together.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Antonio. this is Emily Wright.
And David. right?
Close.
Ryan Wright.
Emily is our editorial writer
and reviewer.
She does what I used to do.
except she's much faster and funnier.
It's good to meet you. Emily.
Oh.
And what do you do for us. Ryan?
Not a lot. to be honest.
I'm an accountant
at a different firm. not here.
I'm just an accessory tonight.
Like a corsage.
Well. we're really excited
to be working with you all.
Us too.
We are very excited.
the feeling's mutual.
And we got a DJ for tonight. and we thought
it'd be cool if everyone picked a song.
So. it's just going to be Mr. Brightside
on loop all night.
Oh. I love that song.
No. no. no.
Pick something that says
something about you.
or how you feel. or something that makes
you feel good. you know?
That does sound like fun.
Well. welcome and enjoy yourselves.
I'm sure we'll talk some more
during the night.
Absolutely. Yes.
It was good to meet you both.
My God!
Nat. this is Ryan. as mentioned.
Ryan. this is my boss. Nat.
Why did I call you David?
Because you're shit with names.
You called me Alyssa for six months.
I did. didn't I?
I mean. you really look like an Alyssa.
And yet. I'm not.
You definitely look like a Ryan.
That's good.
Nat's not usually this awkward.
I'm really not.
Really nervous.
Excuse me.
Are you good?
Yeah.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
This view's nice.
He's cute.
Is this the mysterious lockdown boyfriend?
Ah. he's just on hire.
like an animal rainbow.
but for awkward
introverts at office parties.
Nice.
Can I borrow him?
How are you doing. Nat?
Well. look. this is the
first time I've worn this
since my white dad was
married for the third time.
Is it too gay. be honest?
Really?
You look great.
Just have a couple of vodkas
and you'll loosen right up.
No. not drinking.
Can't drink.
Oh. Nat. that's boring.
I know.
Who cares if he likes you?
He's just the new boss.
I am so glad that you came though.
seriously.
It means a lot.
You said it was mandatory.
I lied.
I'll be back.
Hope you're having a good night.
Okay. so far.
How's pop?
Hey.
How'd you know that?
Lucky guess.
No. I'm kidding. You told me.
When?
I think it was like our second time
chatting on the bus.
What. like three years ago?
You don't drink wine
because you don't like it.
You don't drink the hard stuff because
when you were a teenager. you overdid it
and the smell
just makes you want to vomit.
so you like beer.
but the beer has to be
a little bit fruity.
What's mine?
Whatever's on offer.
Okay. escape plans.
We need to do something
about this situation.
Nat will kill me if I leave.
I thought they'd be drinking
and mingling by now.
We need a distraction.
We might just have fun.
You don't know me.
These are all your people. huh?
It's a complete sausage fest.
It's a very male-dominated sector.
A lot of beards.
They'll probably think you're one of them.
so watch out.
So how did you end up in it?
I didn't want a real job.
Well. well. well.
I lost a bet.
Didn't think you'd show up.
You should have told me.
I would have stayed at home
and we could have split the money.
It was only ten bucks.
Hi. I'm Mike anyway.
Hi. mate. Ryan.
Are you in corporate or creative?
Told you.
No. Ryan has a real job.
Mike reviews the iPhones. but he still
has an Android because he thinks he's edgy.
Yeah. I just prefer an open ecosystem.
What song did you pick. Mike?
Was it Mr. Brightside?
Yeah.
Why?
Ah. just fucking knew it.
This is why I always
have headphones on at work.
Hey. you see Nat. they look stressed in
that outfit.
Like when you put a Christmas sweater
on your pet.
Hey. leave them alone. dick.
What? That's something you'd say.
Yeah. about you.
Uh. I'll be back.
Cool.
See?
Such a bitch.
But I love her.
Like a little sister. of course.
who's also a bitch.
Bored at work. Dead here.
One heart attack.
How's your work thing?
You wanna send me some nudes?
Love ya.
Diet Coke. please?
Hard stuff. huh?
Yeah. the bosses don't get to drink
at these things.
You just have to foot the bill
for the rest of us.
That sounds like a terrible deal to me.
So. I've read a lot of your reviews.
They're good.
In fact. you convinced me to get this.
Smart ring. Really?
Didn't I give that. like. a five?
You gave the sleep tracking an eight.
How's that working for you?
Never been a very good sleeper.
Now you know. for sure.
Yeah.
So how long have you been
with the company?
Yeah. so like.
this rash started developing.
But that's because. like.
we're sitting down all day.
but I try to get up.
And. like. the skin started flaking off.
It wasn't bad. It wasn't bleeding.
Hello. you two.
You behaving yourselves?
Yeah.
Kind of.
What are you're drinking. Nat?
Just juice.
Hey.
You know what. though?
No.
Yes.
You're a bit missing Gary about now.
I'm okay now. We're watching a show.
Thank you. Have a good night.
Love you. Pop.
It's fine.
We make do.
We're not usually this boring.
I promise.
Ah. no. it's all good.
I'm having fun.
Hmm.
Do you want a drink? Drink?
Shit yeah.
Okay.
Nice guy.
So...
where do you see yourself in two years?
Four beers.
I should probably say
'exactly where I am.
but better and making
more money for you.'
Please. you can be honest.
Yeah.
No. I'm not drinking.
Oh. really?
Well. Nat says 'Cheers.'
Oh.
Okay.
Maybe just one.
Here you are. mate.
There's a... Thank you.
Oh. no. no.
That's from Antonio.
He says 'Cheers.'
Oh.
Excuse me for a second.
Okay.
I like beer now.
Do you?
No. I really don't.
Ooh!
You holding up the bar?
I think it's holding me up.
I promise we'll leave soon
and I'll get you a kebab or something.
Are you kidding me?
This is literally the most fun
I've had in years.
Want a drink?
It's on me.
I'm pretty sure it's still an open bar.
Sure.
I might've spent six months
lying on my living room floor
I might've been sick. then well.
then sick some more
I might be prouder of me
Than I ever have been
I've been learning about letting go
How to do it without my claws
scratching the surfaces
I've been learning about wasting time
and closing some doors
Hoping to open more
down the line
Alright. shots!
Oh no. I said I wasn't drinking tonight.
and I've already had three beers.
Come on.
It's his birthday.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay. happy birthday.
Oh. good.
All right. guys.
Nat. we're doing shots.
No. no. no. no.
Hey. it's his birthday.
Really?
Yes!
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Okay. just one. just one.
Go around.
Yeah. right?
Thank you.
Right. on three.
One. two. three.
Happy birthday.
Ah. these fucking shoes!
One more.
This one's on you. Antonio.
Yeah. that's fair.
Okay.
Last one.
Oh. to your team.
To the new team.
Okay.
Whoa.
Oh.
Mike.
Oh. Mike. Go over.
Over the glass. That's it.
Over the glass.
Do you have any Band-aids?
Two please.
Here we go.
Hey. come with me.
Come with me.
One sec. Can I get a water?
Thank you.
Sit down.
All right.
I can do it. I can do it.
I forgot.
I'm wearing pantyhose.
Can you cover me?
Sure.
Good luck.
Okay.
All right.
There we go.
That's it.
Thank you.
All good?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you for plus-one-ing me.
What have I dragged you away from?
What would you normally be doing
on a Saturday night?
Uh. let's see.
Ironing my work clothes.
Maybe watching TV with my grandparents.
You?
Less skirts.
More sweatpants.
Couch.
Buy take-out.
Stalking my old high school friends
on Instagram and Facebook
to make me feel better about my life.
Man. this night has really held us back
from living our best lives. huh?
Was this you?
Really?
That is a bold choice.
Know you target audience.
Here we go.
Wait for it.
Here it comes.
'You don't want anyone.'
Wow.
You read them perfectly.
'Don't tell me'
Well. you assisted.
'this is paradise.'
Can you read me?
What do I need?
Is this your song?
Oh. yours.
Nice. Well done.
I haven't heard this song in years.
Oh. my God.
So...
How are you guys doing?
Great.
I'll be back.
See you in a bit.
Well you look happy.
You know. I don't think I've ever
seen you look happy.
I like this look for you.
Meanwhile. I have the drunk's sweats.
Oh. my God.
I've got to go to Anon.
It's not too bad.
I've been shitting myself all night.
Should we get out of here?
You leapt from crumbling bridges
watching cityscapes turn to dust
Filming helicopters crashing
in the ocean from way above
Got the music in you. baby. tell me why
You've been locked in here forever
and you just can't say goodbye
Kisses on the foreheads
of the lovers wrapped in your arms
You've been hiding them
in hollowed-out pianos left in the dark
Got the music in you. baby. tell me why
You've been locked in here forever
and you just can't say goodbye
Your lips. my lips
Apocalypse
Go and sneak us through the rivers
Flood is rising up on your knees
Oh. please
Come out and haunt me.
I know you want me
Come out and haunt me
Sharing all your secrets with each other
since you were kids
Sleeping soundly with the locket
that she gave you clutched in your fist
Got the music in you. baby. tell me why
Got the music...
Are you okay?
I have a boyfriend.
Why didn't you tell me?
I should go.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-